breaths. It is time to put those rescue breathing
skills to work. Please head back to your mannequins.
We are going to run through several rounds of practice to make sure you feel
confident in delivering these life-saving breaths.
As you practice rescue breaths, your instructor will be checking to ensure
you are getting clear chest rise. Remember, we are not looking for big
forceful blows. We want gentle steady breaths that last
about one second each. Once you've achieved clear chest rise,
practice combining your skills by performing 30 chest compressions
followed by two effective rescue breaths and repeat.
You want to move from compressions to breaths and back again as smoothly and
quickly as possible.